# Wiktor ZIEJEWSKI **1996**



As I'm just starting my adventure with the front-end - I don't have job experience in this field, but I'm willing to learn, discover and become better. I finished a front-end course at Kodilla where I learned HTML CSS JavaScript and React. 'm also familiar with how some of the project's processes look - but I never worked on a tech project in a tech company - so you need to give me some time. I'mooking for a place that will help me to grow, become a better developer by practicing and learning from the more senior team members.

	Skills		
- HTML, CSS, RWD			=
- JavaScript, React			<u> </u>
- Jira, CMS - Git, GitHub		- English B1/B2	— ⊕
-Adobe suite (Photoshop/Illustrator/After	rEffects)		



### **Education**

# 01/2021-06/2021

Front-end course at Kodilla.com school

#### 09/2013 - 06/2017

Technical School No.24 in Warsaw direction: advertising graphics and multimedia specialization:digital graphic process technician



# **Interpesonal skills**

- -Involvement
- -Accuracy
- -Relations hip buliding
- -Openness and honesty
- -Teamwork / Colaboration
- -Self motivation



#### **Experience**

# **07/2022 - 10/2022 Beneko**Apprentice

- -Createing app in React technology
- -Collaborated with developers team

# 09/2020 Ekspresowo

Co-managing in family company

### 06/2017-08/2017 PrintMedia24

PrintingAssistant

- -Operation of printing machines
- -Conceptualizes and creates covers for books
- -Customer service

# **11/2016-05/2017** Addicters advertising agency, Junior Graphic Designer

- -Working as part oft he Brand team with research and development of creative projects
- -Assist in the development and execution of concepts and visual ideas
- -Collaborated with design team in creating graphic